

Anzor Urdia

Q 04/09/1990 ☐ Georgia ② J. Kuperjanovi 2, Tartu 51003, Estonia ☐ +372 59144144 ☑ anzorurdia@gmail.com

Profile

others.

I'm a software engineer with 5+ years of working experience.

I've worked on multiple different web apps written on .NET(MVC) and for the last 3 years I've been focused on Ruby and Rails. I have worked on projects such as Crypto wallets, enterprise billing software, all-in-one healthcare application and

My strength is in easily finding optimal and efficient ways of overcoming challenges while building clean structure and logic. I'm open to new challenges.

Strengths

Collaboration Leadership Delegation

Quick Learning Reliable Solution Architecture

Work experience

Software Engineer Freelancer at Upwork.com

Freelancer Software Engineer, RoR developer

- . Norwegian BankID, Vipps(Norway's Mobile Payments App), Visma integrations into the system.
- . Elasticsearch, Search Functionality module for system.
- . Custom CRM/CSM MVP for Norway company.

Link:

https://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/~015babbe6fa1a897d8/progress using appropriate tools.

Software Engineer Vabaco Ltd.

Worked on healthcare and billing software for the clinics and the hospitals.

Work experience

- . Designed and Implemented a new hospitalization module, it helps clinics and hospitals to digitalize their hospitalization and treatment processes.
- . Designed and Implemented integration, communication, and exchange information with different systems, such as "Ministry of IDPs from the occupied territories, labor, health and social affairs of Georgia" and National health agency.

Worked on healthcare app, called Ekimo.

- . For development, it was used Engines.
- Designed and Implemented a medicine ordering module, Integration with pharmacy companies.
- · Designed and Implemented an insurance module, Integration with insurance companies, and insurance processes.
- . Designed and Implemented user sensitive data encryption API.
- . Designed and Implemented different type of promotions module.

Job-related skills:

- Ability to handle highly stressed situations and unexpected errors in an efficient manner.
- Working with a core team and a scrum master.
- Coding, testing and fixing programming errors.
- Conceptual, logical and physical database design.
- Custom report projects, optimizing existing database tables to handle variety of queries.
- Develop and maintain applications passing through all stages.
- Implementation of new projects, the integration of existing services.
- Interacted with QA team, solving bugs through a trouble ticket system.
- Participate in project planning, provide realistic time estimates for units of work, update and track
- Planning, architect and developing web applications from the ground up.

Ħ 06/2017 - 07/2018 ♥ TBILISI, GEORGIA

Ruby on Rails Developer

Ruby on Rails Developer Birtvi. Ltd.

Work experience

Worked on Cryptocurrency e-Wallet and exchange platform

- . Designed and Implemented Cryptocurrency hot and cold e-Wallet, transactions, saving.
- . Designed and Implemented different Cryptocurrencies, such as Ethereum, Litecoin, Dashcoin.

IT Community Development Manager Georgia's Innovation and Technology Agency

Worked on ICT community development.

. Planning and executing IT infrastructure development and training projects to nurture the tech community in the startup ecosystem.

Ħ 05/2015 - 01/2016 ♥ TBILISI, GEORGIA

Web developer Helix Ltd.

Worked as a web developer

. Creating landing and commercial websites for different clients

Skills

i LANGUAGES Gerogian English Russian i PROGRAMING LANGUAGES, FRAMEWORKS, TOOLS

Rails
Ruby
Ruby engines
Redis
Rabbitmq
Sidekiq
Swagger
C#
ElasticSearch
Javascript
React

CLOUD
Heroku

O POSTGRE SQL

AWS Hatchbox

Database Administration Database Migration

(i) NETWORK Load Balancers - HLB, NLB, GTM

Education

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng) Georgian Technical University

Ħ 09/2007 - 12/2009 🤈 TBILISI, GEORGIA

Bachelor Degree - Economics Ivane Javakhishvili Tbilisi State University

Hobbies







New Technology



Swimming



Music



Meditation